Oghenetega Akpowenre

Front-End Web Developer

Lagos

oghenetegaakpowenre@gmail.com

+234 817 037 6604

I'm a front-end web developer with considerable work experience in the IT industry. I'm passionate about building beautiful and effective products for the web. You can check out some of my work on my portfolio at https://otega99.github.io

Personal Details

Date Of Birth: 1999-12-29 **Industry:** Software Development **NYSC Status:** Completed

Work Experience

Intern

Cyberspace Limited - Lagos August 2019 to January 2020

- Developed an API in C# for handling user login and signup which was implemented in the back-end logic of a banking application being developed by the company.
- Contributed to the development of an advert management software called Publicité. My specific role was to develop a middleware in C# which determined if a user was attempting to access an expired database and if so deny the user access to the database and notify him/her of the database status, with an email using the SendGrid API.
- Supervised the repair of a damaged company server.
- Supervised the transfer of sensitive company equipment from one branch to another.

Intern

Radix Pensions Managers Limited - Lagos July 2018 to September 2018

- Assisted in training the marketing department on the use of a data-capture device.
- Supervised the installation of an inverter and a broadband satellite dish.
- Addressed system connectivity issues.
- Created and edited sensitive documents and financial spreadsheets.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

University of Benin 2017 to 2021

Skills

- Sass (2 years)
- HTML (4 years)
- Javascript (4 years)
- Github (4 years)
- Python (4 years)
- C# (3 years)
- React (2 years)
- Node JS (2 years)

Languages

• English - Expert

Links

http://github.com/otega99

http://otega99.github.io

Certifications and Licenses

Responsive Web Design (freecodecamp.org)

July 2021 to Present

This certification can be verified at

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/otega99/responsive-web-design

Scientific Computing with Python (freecodecamp.org)

May 2021 to Present

This certification can be verified at

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/otega99/scientific-computing-with-python-v7

Data Analysis with Python (freecodecamp.org)

June 2021 to Present

This certification can be verified at

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/otega99/data-analysis-with-python-v7